MARTON KEREK



PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name: Marton Kerek

Telephone Number: 07522 916928 E-mail: kerekmarci@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a motivated and experienced manager with a strong background in hotel operation. With my unique passion and approach, I was successfully leading various teams, improved guest satisfaction and coached team members on different levels. I am also a member of the AICR (Association for Front Office Managers) as I really enjoy meeting people in the same industry and with the same interest.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Oct. 2018 to present

Park Plaza Westminster Bridge London

4-star, 1019-bedroom hotel in central London

Senior Guest Relations Manager

- o head of the Guest Relations department, including 5 Guest Relations Managers and 2 Guest Relations Hosts
- o from December 2019 to February 2020, I was in charge of the **Guest Services** department as well of 22 team members in the absence of Guest Services Manager
- o covering Reception Manager shifts in the absence of the Reception Manager
- o enhance services for regular and VIP guests by personalising their experience
- o ensure that Guest Relations Managers are fully trained on handling and resolving complaints, responding to emergencies and escalation procedures are followed
- o analyse guest reviews, trends improved problem resolution by 8% from last year
- o create succession plans for the team, improved staff retention by 14%
- o replaced gift order menu and selection, with an increase of revenue by 20% YOY
- o being the Health and Safety representative for Reception and Guest Relations, creating departmental risk assessments and health & safety trainings
- o familiar with crisis management, emergencies, lock-down procedures

July 2017-Oct. 2018 **Holiday Inn London-Camden Lock** London 4-star. 130-bedroom hotel in central London

Guest Services Manager

- o act as a Reception Manager, including covering Duty Manager shifts
- o manage Reception, look after Rota, payroll and compliance with brand standards
- o recruit, coach and develop new team members
- o handle emergencies and escalated complaints
- o evaluate and improve levels of guest satisfaction
- o implement procedures to improve efficiency within the department, across other departments to drive guest experience
- o respond to reviews on social media platforms, such as TripAdvisor
- o successfully implemented an incentive system at Front Office

Aug. 2015-July 2017 London Hilton on Park Lane London

5-star, 453-room hotel in London's exclusive Mayfair district

Front Office Supervisor

- o motivate and train Team to ensure all KPIs are met
 - reaching the highest yearly departmental upsell in the hotel history
 - achieved 99% realisation rate on eStandby upgrades
 - led a project on increasing Efficiency of Arrival that resulted in 5% increase compared to previous year
- o writing and conducting Performance Development Reviews
- o cover Duty Manager and Guest Relations shifts

June 2013-Aug. 2015 Hilton Budapest

Budapest

5-star, 322-room luxury hotel in a World Heritage Site

Night Manager

- o supervise the Front Office and other departments during night
- o take full responsibility of the hotel in the shift as a Duty Manager
- o streamline daily procedures in accordance to Hilton Standards
- o established complete Night Manager and Night Auditor shift procedures after switching to Opera PMS
- o become the Employee of 4th quarter in 2014

June 2012-June 2013 Estilo Fashion Hotel

Budapest

4-star, 70-room boutique hotel downtown

Front Desk Receptionist/Shift Leader and Reservation Agent

- o taking active part in pre-opening of the hotel
- o perform day and night shifts, reconcile money and run night audit
- o all aspects of reservation tasks, including Extranet surface for OTAs
- o achieved the yearly highest sales record in the team

May to Oct. 2011 **Danubius Hotel Gellért**

Budapest

renowned 4-star, 234-bedroom historical hotel

• Receptionist and Reservation Agent during university studies

EDUCATION

2009-2013 Budapest Business School

Budapest

 College of Commerce, Catering and Tourism, faculty of catering trade and hotel management

2013: Foreign Exchange Clerk

COMPUTER LITERACY

Opera, Micros, OnQ, HotSOS, Adaco, Fourth, Talos ATS, various CRM systems

LANGUAGES

Hungarian: Native | English: Advanced | French: Medium Level